[Verse 1]
Midnight reflections on the court
A game of speed, a brand new sport
You move to the left, I cut to the right
Electric silhouettes in violet light
[Pre-Chorus]
Every heartbeat syncs to the beat
Feel the rhythm rising beneath our feet
[Chorus]
Oh, neon velocity, take the floor!
One more touch and we want some more!
Spinning around in the golden glow,
We set the tempo wherever we go!
[Funky Bass Fill]
[Verse 2]
Angles and glass, the city shines
We’re drawing circles through the painted lines
[Chorus]
Oh, neon velocity, take the floor!
One more touch and we want some more!
Spinning around in the golden glow,
We set the tempo wherever we go!
[Outro]
Velocity...
Fade into the night.